<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>

    <!-- Category Names -->
    <string name="markets">Markets</string>
    <string name="general_markets">Markets</string>
    <string name="food_markets">Food Markets</string>
    <string name="attractions">Attractions</string>
    <string name="free_attractions">Free Attractions</string>
    <string name="paid_attractions">Paid Attractions</string>
    <string name="restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="vegan_restaurants">Vegan Restaurants</string>
    <string name="vegan_friendly_restaurants">Vegan Friendly Restaurants</string>

    <!--MarketsFragment addresses-->
    <string name="camden_market_address"></string>
    <string name="portobello_market_address"></string>
    <string name="covent_market_address"></string>
    <string name="greenwich_market_address"></string>
    <string name="old_spitafields_market_address"></string>
    <string name="brick_lane_market_address"></string>
    <string name="alfies_antique_market_address"></string>
    <string name="broadway_market_address"></string>
    <string name="southbank_market_address"></string>
    <string name="maltby_market_address"></string>
    <string name="columbia_market_address"></string>

    <!--FoodMarketsFragment addresses-->
    <string name="name_market_address"></string>

    <!-- MarketsFragment Description Strings -->
    <string name="camden_market_description">Camden Lock is at the heart of Camden Town\'s thriving markets area.
        Open seven days per week, Camden Lock Market comprises stalls and shops selling everything from vintage
        clothing to hand-made jewellery and artwork to gifts, music and more. There are also food stalls offering
        a large variety of cuisines. \n\nA former timber yard for ship builders TE Dingwalls, Camden Lock was
        opened in the 1970s as Camden\'s original arts and crafts market. The original market hall was re-opened
        in the 1980s and a steel and glass canopy added to the East Yard in 2003.</string>

    <string name="portobello_market_description">Portobello Road has been a market since the 1800s but became
        particularly famous for its antiques in the 1950s. Now there are numerous stalls offering everything
        from fruit and bread to posters, clothes, ceramics and music.\n\nEasily accessible from Notting Hill
        Gate, Ladbroke Grove and Westbourne Park tube station and by bus routes servicing Ladbroke Grove and
        Notting Hill Gate. Main market days are Friday and Saturday with a smaller market running Monday to
        Thursday. An exciting day out for all the family.</string>

    <string name="covent_market_description">Once home to the world-famous fruit and vegetable market, Covent
        Garden’s Apple Market continues to support market traders, offering a range of unique handmade crafts
        and goods throughout the week.\n\nFrom Tuesday to Sunday, the Apple Market is filled with handmade
        jewellery, prints, watercolours and beautiful crafts and every Monday, you’ll find one-off antiques
        and collectables.\n\nOpen every day of the week, the East Colonnade Market has a variety of stalls
        selling products such as handmade soap, jewellery, handbags, hand-knitted children's clothing, a
        magician's stall, sweets, artwork and homeware.\n\nIn the South Piazza, the Jubilee Market changes
        its wares daily. On Mondays, the market is dedicated to antiques. From Tuesday to Friday, a general
        market operates with traders selling clothes and household goods. At weekends, the market offers arts
        and crafts.</string>

    <string name="greenwich_market_description">Greenwich Market is packed full of unique and distinctive
        arts and crafts. Well known for its designer makers and small cottage industries, customers have
        access to items that cannot be found anywhere else in the world. Enjoy the vibrant atmosphere,
        take in some classical music performed by students from nearby Trinity College of Music, and enjoy
        the continental food court whilst browsing through the wonderful array of over 120 arts, craft
        and antique stalls.\n\n Tues: antiques, vintage, collectables and food. Wed: crafts and food-to-go.
        Thurs: crafts, antiques and vintage. Fri-Sun: arts, crafts, fresh produce and food-to-go. Every day:
        specialist shops and pubs.</string>

    <string name="old_spitafields_market_description">Old Spitalfields Market is one of the finest
        surviving Victorian Market Halls in London (built 1876)./n/nStalls sell antiques, food and
        fashion, varying from distinct and quirky creations from up-and-coming designers to bohemian,
        vintage and African designs. Boutiques offer everything from hand-crafted wooden toys to today\'s
        must-have design items.\n\nThe mix of well-known chain restaurants and fresh food market stalls
        provide a gastronomic paradise for discerning food lovers and families alike. High quality
        and affordable cuisine on offer includes deli-style dishes, fresh produce, artisan breads
        and plenty of organic and fair trade products.</string>

    <string name="brick_lane_market_description">Brick Lane Market is a large East End flea market
        with street stalls selling antiques, clothes and bric-a-brac at bargain prices.\n\nSince 2000
        Brick Lane has seen several markets open under the The Truman Markets umbrella: the Boiler
        House Food Hall, the Tea Rooms, the Backyard Market, the Sunday UpMarket, and the Vintage Market.
        These markets sell everything from vintage and handmade clothing, accessories, jewellery, music,
        arts and crafts, and tasty street food. The food trucks are in the yard seven days a week.\n\n\
        The markets are open at the Old Truman Brewery on Brick Lane on Saturday between 11am-6pm and
        Sunday from 10am-5pm, except the Sunday UpMarket which is just on Sunday and the Vintage Market
        which is also open on Thursday and Friday.</string>

    <string name="alfies_antique_market_description">Alfies Antique Market is a bustling and lively
        centre for decorative and unusual antiques. This chic and cheerful market has a little more
        life than your traditional antique thoroughfares, boasting some 75 specialist dealers, spread
        over five floors. On the top floor you'll find the Roof Top Kitchen where you can enjoy
        panoramic views over London’s rooftops.</string>

    <string name="broadway_market_description">One of the oldest chartered markets in London is
        having a revival. Broadway Market is a buzzing centre of the community. The market includes a
        farmer\'s market stocking an eclectic mix of goods from local farmers, artists and craftspeople.
        \n\nWith shops and galleries selling local art, a ceramics shop selling original pieces and
        artisans selling a mixture of exciting and unusual clothes and gifts, the street offers unusual
        and stunning merchandise at affordable prices.</string>

    <string name="southbank_market_description">Search for fresh food and drink from small producers
        and independent traders at the Southbank Centre Market every weekend.\n\nHeld every Friday
        to Sunday on Southbank Centre Square, behind the Royal Festival Hall, this market features
        more than 40 producers, including specialists in meats, spices, confectionary and more.
        You can take the delicious produce home, or sample yummy dishes cooked on site.</string>

    <string name="maltby_market_description">A small but bustling market offering fresh produce,
        including breads, cakes, meats and cheeses. Popular sellers include Monty\'s Deli sandwiches
        and St John Bakery's sourdough and fresh filled doughnuts. The Kernel Brewery is also open
        during market time.</string>

    <string name="columbia_market_description">Sited in London\'s East End, near Brick Lane and
        Spitalfields, this street market has a friendly atmosphere and is open every Sunday from
        8am to 3pm.\n\nColumbia Road is lined with 60 independent shops, including small art
        galleries, cupcake shops, vintage clothes stores, garden and antique shops, and English
        and Italian delis. There are also numerous pubs, cafes and restaurants in which to
        refuel.</string>

    <!-- MarketsFragment Days Open Strings -->
    <string name="camden_market_openning_times">OPENING TIMES: \n\nCamden Lock market is open seven
        days a week, every day except Christmas Day.</string>

    <string name="portobello_market_openning_times">OPENING TIMES: \n\nMonday - Wednesday: 09:00
        - 18:00 and Thursday: 09:00 - 13:00 and Friday and Saturday: 09:00 - 19:00</string>

    <string name="covent_market_openning_times">OPENING TIMES: \n\nEveryday 10am until 6pm</string>

    <string name="greenwich_market_openning_times">OPENING TIMES: \n\nTuesday to Sunday and Bank
        Holidays 10:00 to 17:30.</string>

    <string name="old_spitafields_market_openning_times">OPENING TIMES: \n\nRestaurants open daily
        - hours vary. Shops open daily - hours varying but generally 11.00 - 19.00.</string>

    <string name="brick_lane_market_openning_times">OPENING TIMES: \n\nOpen Sunday only 10:00 -
        17:00</string>

    <string name="alfies_antique_market_openning_times">OPENING TIMES: \n\nTuesday - Saturday:
        10:00-18:00</string>

    <string name="broadway_market_openning_times">OPENING TIMES: \n\nSaturday 09:00 - 17:00</string>

    <string name="southbank_market_openning_times">OPENING TIMES: \n\nFriday: 12:00 -20:00,
        Saturday: 11:00 -20:00, Sunday: 12:00 - 18:00, Monday (bank holidays only) 12:00 - 18:00</string>

    <string name="maltby_market_openning_times">OPENING TIMES: \n\nThe market is open Saturdays
        between 9am-4pm and Sundays between 11am-4pm</string>

    <string name="columbia_market_openning_times">OPENING TIMES: \n\nSunday 08:00 – 15:00 (closing
        time approximate)</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close</string>

</resources>
